A Guide to the Papers of Virginius Dabney, 1942-1980
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Virginius Dabney 1942-1980
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
7690-ad
This collection consists of 2 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited on 11 November 1980.
Contents List
- Notes and Research Material for Across the Years
  - Youth and Evington, also Paris 1960, 1963, 1974, 1975, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Episcopal High School 1968, 1975-1976, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Views of Society and the World 1951-1965, 1974-1977, n.d. (Box 1)
  - University of Virginia and Ivory Tower 1950, 1964, 1968, 1974-1976, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Teacher at Episcopal High School, Reporter and Marriage, Europe 1927 and 1934 1975, 1976, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Chief Editorial Writer and Editor, 1934-1945 1942-1949, 1977, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Editor, 1946-1953 1971, 1976, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Editor, 1954-1969 1953, 1954, 1962-1977, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Journalism Data 1963-1977, n.d., 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Branch Spalding 1956-1957, 1977, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Father and Mother (Lucy) 1970, 1976, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Retirement 1966, 1975-1978, n.d. (Box 1)
- Reviews and Correspondence: Across the Years
  - Correspondence between Virginius Dabney and Doubleday re Across the Years1975-1979, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Correspondence re: Across the Years1978-1980, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Across the Years: Reviews and Advertisements 1978-1979, n.d. (Box 2)